http://www.earthlyadornments.com/pages/sales-policies-and-faqs

International Shipping Alert
Due to the Covid 19 pandemic, all US Postal Service international shipments are sent to a local hub in Hayward, California, to await air transport to the destination. This is causing sometimes significant delays. FedEx international shipments seem to provide faster delivery. This situation is temporary and shipment delivery times are expected to return to normal when the pandemic subsides.
Shipping & Delivery
We ship all items USPS or UPS within and outside of the United States. Shipping prices are weight based. We are not responsible for uninsured packages. You may include insurance as an option to your shipping method during checkout. Although we most often ship the same day orders are received, we guarantee shipment with 48 hours of receipt of order and/or payment. We ship during business hours 9am to 5pm Pacific Standard Time Monday through Friday. We do not ship on weekends.
International Orders
We are glad to take overseas orders to most countries. We accept PayPal, Visa, MasterCard and American Express. Customs declarations will be filled out accurately as required by U.S. law. It is up to you to check with your country's customs rules and other fees. Please don't ask us to falsify any customs information or values. We value our international customers and will work with you to get the best possible safe shipping rates.
We insure all international parcels. We have no way to track USPS first class.  If you want your order to be tracked please select Priority Mail International of FedEx Priority International.  We insure all international packages.  If you package is lost you must wait 45 days before we can place an insurance claim.
Expedited Orders
We normally process and ship orders in the order received. If your package cannot wait 3 days to ship and needs to get out immediately, please email or telephone us for expedited shipping and we will do our best to accommodate you.
Privacy Policy
We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy.
We will collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address and phone number when you make a purchase from us. We do not have access to or retain your credit card information.  We do not share your information with any third party. Your personal information will never be sold or made available to any other company or service.
We use your personal information to process and fulfill your order, including sending you emails to confirm your order status and shipment. We may need to contact you to resolve a problem in order to complete your order, at which time we will attempt to contact you by email or telephone.
Return Policy
We pride ourselves on customers' satisfaction.  Although it is our intention to display images and descriptions of each item that are true to material, color, size, etc., colors vary with individual monitors and some item details are inevitably missed. We recognize that the buyer is deprived of the tactile and visual experience when purchasing on the web.
Therefore, if you are not satisfied with your purchase, we will gladly refund your purchase price provided that you contact within three days of receipt and that you ship the merchandise back to us within one week in the same condition in which you received it. For your own protection, we suggest that you purchase shipping insurance. We cannot accept returns of jewelry damaged after your receipt. You are responsible for return shipping and insurance. Your refund will be transacted within 3 days in the same manner of your remittance, i.e. credit card, PayPal or check.
If you have questions or concerns about an item you’re interested in, please email us at sales@earthlyadornments.com with your questions and we’ll get back to you within 24 hours, or call us at 707-823-8978.
Quantity Discounts
Much of our bead collection is the result of many hours in thrift stores, closeout warehouses, yard sales, flea markets, antique stores and acquisitions of dealer collections. Some of our other beads are unused vintage stock, also purchased more than 30 years ago. As a result, quantities of many of our vintage beads are very limited -- and we feel that those beads are all the more special and rare because we can't replace them once they are sold. Given the time invested in seeking them out over the years -- and given that they are irreplaceable -- we are not offering quantity discounts on vintage stock.
We will negotiate quantity discounts on some new stock that can be reordered. Feel free to contact us
We are happy to answer any questions you may have about any of the pieces you see -- or any pieces you don't see, because not all of our collection is currently online! We have a large collection of vintage jewelry, beads and components that we have not listed-- so please don't hesitate to email us.
Layaway
Layaway is available for jewelry purchases over $300. We require 1/3 of the total invoice at inception of layaway, 1/3 in 30 days and 1/3 in 60 days. Please email or call us for arrangements.
We buy vintage and antique jewelry
Home
Jewelry
Jewelry By Era
Victorian & Art Nouveau Jewelry
Edwardian and Arts & Crafts Jewelry
Art Deco Jewelry
1900-1920 Jewelry
Mozambique
Myanmar (Burma)
Namibia
Nauru
Nepal
Netherlands
Netherlands Antilles
New Caledonia
New Zealand
Nicaragua
Zimbabwe
AlabamaAlaskaAmerican SamoaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFederated States of MicronesiaFloridaGeorgiaGuamHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarshall IslandsMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNorthern Mariana IslandsOhioOklahomaOregonPalauPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirgin IslandsVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
Shipping Methods
